{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is my name?",
      "options": ["Ali", "Mohammad", "Joe", "Peter"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "How old am I?",
      "options": ["20 yo", "15 yo", "13 yo", "18 yo"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is my job and dream field?",
      "options": ["Software developer", "medical", "pilot", "engineer"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Where did I born?",
      "options": ["Erbil", "Najaf", "Mosul", "Basra"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is my dream university?",
      "options": [
        "MIT",
        "Kufa university",
        "Stanford university",
        "others.."
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is my favourite food?",
      "options": ["Pasta", "Biryani", "burger", "Kabab"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is my dream city?",
      "options": [
        "Moscow",
        "Ankara",
        "Roma",
        "NYC"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "My favourite football team?",
      "options": [
        "Real Madrid",
        "Manchester city",
        "Barcelona",
        "Napoli"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the GOAT?",
      "options": [
        "Beckham",
        "diego Maradona",
        "Pele",
        "Lionel Messi"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "My favourite game console?",
      "options": [
        "Xbox",
        "Pc",
        "Nintendo",
        "Playstation"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "My favourite game?",
      "options": [
        "Call of duty",
        "Horizon frobidden west",
        "Uncharted",
        "God of war"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "My phone brand is : ?",
      "options": ["Samsung", "iphone", "Realmi", "Honor"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "My education level is : ?",
      "options": [
        "Primary",
        "Intermediate",
        "University",
        "Preparatory"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "My favourite movie is : ?",
      "options": [
        "Interstellar",
        "Ambulance",
        "My fault",
        "Lucy"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "My favourite song is : ?",
      "options": [
        "Way down we go",
        "Love story",
        "Childhood",
        "Diamonds"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    }
  ]
}
